Che-Wei Chang

Kaohsiung City, Taiwan $\square +886$ [972-346-890] \square adwx1973@gmail.com |

Summary

With two-year experience in IT field, I possess versatile mid-level technical skills: full-stack programming, web scraping and database, as well as product-oriented skills: mobile app UI/UX design and agile development flow.

Both MIS and MBA background cultivates myself as a proactive, flexible, and creative person. Besides, currently I am studying further essential basics(AI, Data Analysis, Machine Learning, etc.) for being a data engineer and working around the world.

EXPERIENCE

WAU YUAN PROPERTY APPRAISAL CO., LTD.

Kaohsiung, Taiwan

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

March 2018 - October 2018

- Collected data via web scraping for building financial databases (Python/MariaDB).
- Developed and maintained a web-based financial valuation system(Spring MVC/AngularJS).

MONMOUTH TECHNOLOGIES, INC.

Kaohsiung, Taiwan

SYSTEM ANALYST

June 2016 - March 2017

- Analyzed customer demand and write user-stories for standard version of PM system.
- Designed UI/UX interfaces and make manuals/SPECS for customized mobile apps.
- Coordinated with departments of Sales and RD: such as planning PM SOP for each product developing cycle, user acceptance tests, etc.

LEQUIOS SOFT INC. (Kaohsiung Branch)

Kaohsiung, Taiwan

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

December 2014 - December 2015

- Developed partial modules of a large-scale disaster-prevention system on Windows and Linux.
- Assisted Japanese team to track and fix product bugs, including web pages(Html/CSS/JavaScript), user-interfaces, databases(MySQL) and system modules(C/Perl/Shell Script).

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: C, Java(Spring MVC), Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript(AngularJS), MySQL/MariaDB
- Technologies: Git, SPSS(Statistics), Axure(UI/UX)
- Languages: Chinese (Native), English (Intermediate): IELTS 6.0/TOEIC 750, Japanese (Intermediate): JLPT N1, French (Basic)

EDUCATION

National Sun Yat-Sen University

Kaohsiung, Taiwan

Master's Degree in Management Information System; GPA 3.91

2011 - 2015

Coursework: Multivariate Analysis; Production/Operation Management; Digital Marketing; Marketing Management; Logistic Management Systems in Asia/Pacific Area; System Simulation and Analysis; Advanced Operations Research

Ecole Supérieure des Sciences Commerciales d'Angers

Angers, France

One-Year dual master's degree(NSYSU/ESSCA) in International Business

2013 - 2014

Coursework: Cross Cultural Management; Supply Chain Management; Project Management; International Business; Crisis Management: Product and Process Innovation

National Taiwan University of Science and Technology

Taipei, Taiwan

Bachelor's Degree in Management Information System

2007 - 2011

Coursework: Calculus; Programming Language; Mathematics for Management; Data Structures; Statistics; Algorithms; Web pages Development; Database Management Systems; Information Networks; Operating Systems; Management Information System; Operations Research; Discrete Mathematics; System Analysis and Design